Another factor in understanding this administration's policy of appeasement is its relationship with an organization you may not have heard of before,
one of the largest, most powerful organizations in the world, and you should know its name.
It's called the Organization for Islamic Cooperation, Organization for Islamic Cooperation, OIC, and so far it's gone virtually unnoticed.
Who are they? The OIC is the second largest intergovernmental organization in the world after the United Nations.
The OIC claims they have authority to represent all Muslims, even those who live in non-Muslim countries like the United States.
In 2005, this very influential Islamic organization published a 10-year plan of action in 2005
to implement its Sharia-based speech code requirements worldwide.
Listen very carefully to what I'm telling you right now.
It explains this week.
They had a 10-year plan of action to implement their Sharia-based, Islamist-based speech code requirements worldwide.
But don't take my word for it.
They published this plan on their website in English so no one would miss their intent.
They intend to internationally criminalize all communication or any communication or speech
that's deemed by them to be insulting to Islam.
even in countries like the United States.
That, my friends, explains the story of this week.
Islamic-enforced speech codes,
no one, not Muslims, not non-Muslims,
not Americans are allowed to say anything Islamists see
as insulting to their religion.
They intend to force us to kiss our freedom of speech and religion goodbye,
And that's why we're being forewarned today.
Unbelievably, last December they succeeded with both President Obama and Secretary of State Hillary Clinton's help
because they pushed through the United Nations the passage of UN Resolution 1618,
which called upon all countries to enact laws preventing derogatory references to Islam.
A clear violation of our First Amendment freedom of speech.
And even before that, in October, last October, many prominent Islamic organizations wrote a letter to the White House where they urged our White House to do a complete purge of any federal training materials from references to the ideology of Islam.
to ensure that all trainers in our U.S. military, our FBI, and other U.S. security agencies be retrained
so they would be brainwashed in political correctness toward Islam.
That's enforced Islamic speech codes here in the United States.
而这一切都是在我们总统和国务卿的帮助下完成的。
奥巴马政府仅用了几天时间就回复了伊斯兰主义者的这封要求信，
并承诺与这些组织成立一个特别工作组，立即开始对我们的反恐培训进行前所未有的清洗
覆盖所有联邦机构。
真是令人震惊，前所未有。
但当国会议员，包括我在内，开始询问是谁
在我们的政府中领导这次清洗，以及他们
从我们的培训材料中清洗了什么，奥巴马政府告诉我们这些信息
是保密的。
是机密的。
我们不能知道是谁在幕后操纵。
我的朋友们，我在这里说，我们现在已经很晚了。
我们正在迅速失去作为国家的自我认同感，并且正在失去识别我们激进伊斯兰敌人的能力。
现在是本周，为了我们的自由和价值观，我们应该毫不羞耻地站出来，并为我们世界各地的敌人划下一条明确的红线。